(Raj:)-He'll have a Shirley Temple.
-And don't be chintzy with the Shirley.
(Raj:)-Okay, let's check out the females.
-All right.
(Sheldon:)There's a female.
(Raj:)That's Professor Wilkinson's wife.
She's like 80.
(Sheldon:)But she's female. Isn't that the game?
(Raj:)-No. I'm looking for a hookup.
-Oh, yes.
(Sheldon:)So the point of this exercise is for you
to find someone to copulate with?
(Raj:)Not so loud. But ideally, yes.
(Raj:)-Thanks.
-Thank you.
(Sheldon:)And what is my function as wingman?
(Raj:)-You help me run my game.
-Okay.
And what is your game?
(Sheldon:)When I lie through my teeth to a woman,
you nod and agree.
(Girl:)Hey, that's pretty cool. What is it?
(Sheldon:)It's a limited edition
Green Lantern lantern.
(Sheldon:)My friend is looking for someone
to copulate with.